(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-30T00:21:37.945295",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": false,
"max_retries_exceeded": true,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.7-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Hey, were you looking at my Raora?
No, I wasn't!
Raora already hugs me lots, it's...
...first-come, first-served.
What are you even talking about?
No, she's mine! Mine! Mine! She's mine now!
Don't take her! No, it's mine!
Raora's mine now! No, mine! Mine! Mine!
Mine! Mine! Mine! Mine! Mine!
J!
What on earth are you playing over here?
The jealousy game.
The jealousy game?
Yep!
And shouldn't you play something more appropriate for a five-year-old?
Mom, I'm five, and this is what five-year-olds do.
And Dad thought this was funny.
Oh, your dad and I are definitely having a conversation about this later.
Alrighty, it's time for your favorite thing.
Justice!
Justice! Justice!
J, what do you like so much about...
I love Justice.
They make loads of trouble.
What?!
Look, it's starting!
Justice! Justice!
Justice! Justice! Yeah!
How to Protect JUSTICE!
Members of Justice are expected to possess strength,
sound judgment,
and an unwavering sense of justice.
In this training video,
you will learn the fundamental skills and exercises
required of every Justice member.
Now, join us and say it together:
FOR JUSTICE!
The first training is a body search.
Conducted immediately after securing a subject,
even the slightest oversight can lead to serious incidents
or the destruction of evidence,
making this one of the most critical police procedures.
Can Justice keep their emotions in check under any circumstances
and carry out a precise body search to completion?
Stop, ma'am! No further, no further.
It is uh... policy and I'll be conducting a body search.
Come here, madam. Yes, body search you here.
You really insist?
Over here, over here, over here, ma'am.
Okay, okay.
Do you have any electronics, tablets, laptops, devices...?
Wait wait wait, ah!
Turn around here, ma'am.
Like that?
Arms up. All right. Spread your arms, there we go.
Wonderful, wonderful. All right.
What is this?
Uh, you know chattini, you see, my chattini...
They're always hungry, and they really want some food sometimes,
so I always have a emergency cucumber, you know?
Ah, emer- emergency rations. I see, I see, I see.
We can't have that on this premises, I'm sorry.
Ay, I take care of them, huh?
All right, spread your legs, ma'am, over here.
My legs?
Over here, ma'am. Over here, right here.
What are you gonna do if I don't do it? Haha.
Uh, probably arrest you, put you in jail for many years, and...
You arrest me? Really?
take you to court.
You gonna arrest me? What are you gonna do?
Yes.
Oh, what if I... What if I check on you instead?
No one ever stops me.
No, that's my job, ma'am. My job. Over here, ma'am.
Okay, okay.
All right.
Stand there. What is this?
Oh? Ah!
What?
I like cooking. Would you like something?
Maybe I can cook something for you?
Ma'am, I'm a professional. No dating on the job.
Pasta...
Don't you want a little bit of pasta? I'm so good at making pasta!
Well, I am a I'm a bit hungry. Hmm...
Hey, hey, hey! Stop trying to tempt me! Stop trying to tempt me! Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Okay, okay.
All right. Co- Stand here. Stand here, ma'am. Right here now!
She's kind of hot when she's...
Three! Two! One! Arms out! All right, let's see.
And what is this?
Oh, you took it! Ah!
Oh, that's a... What? That's a... That's a chattino jetpack!
Oh, no one should see this. Okay, get out of here.
Ma'am! You... You just threw that small little creature! What?
Ah, don't worry about it.
All right, anyway, what is this?
Are you gonna punish me? Ah!
Oh. Well, you have a lot of food-related items on you, ma'am.
Ma'am, you have a lot of food-related items. Yes.
Yeah, please please eat that before you go over into the premises.
Do you want a little bit too?
No, ma'am. I'm on the job! I'm on the job!
Anyway, ma'am, arms up! Come here, come here, over here.
And what are you gonna do if I don't do it? Want to punish me or something?
Uh, maybe, if you don't come over here right now.
I'm misbehaving! Haha! Not gonna do it! What are you gonna do about it?
Gonna make you do 10 push-ups outside of this training.
Maybe I can do some squats for you?
Ah! What is this?!
No! No, not this one!
No! I can I can explain! Uh, you know, I'm an artist, and uh...
All right. An artist.
I can explain! I can explain!
Anatomy book.
That's my anatomy book!
Uh...
Ma'am, you are way too suspicious! You are under arrest, and also for...
Under arrest? Really?
having chattinis with jetpacks? That is unbelievable!
You are a bad, bad kitty! You are a bad kitty! Come here!
All right, you are under arrest!
Oh, yes, I am! Haha!
Yeah, you Yeah, that was really good, Raora. That was good, yeah.
Yeah, that's it? Yeah? Are we going to jail? Are you gonna bring me to the jail?
That's it for the training. That's it for the training, Raora.
Are we going to sleep together?
Raora, no! We're done with the training! We're done! Hey, we're done with the movie! Hey!
No? Hey, wait! You need to feed me! Let's sleep together!
All right then!
Officer Cecilia Immergreen will be con—
Conducting the body search.
Stop right there!
Hands up in the air!
Wait, I didn't do anything wrong!
Do I have your consent to do a body search on you?
No, no! I didn't do anything wrong!
Do I have your consent? Okay, okay.
Let us see... Let us see what you have here.
I didn't do anything wrong! On what charges?!
What is this?
Nothing.
That's mine! Why did you take that from me?!
It's not. We never met before. Why would I take something from you?
No, I can't believe you would steal. What are you, a thief?!
I did not steal it!
You are under arrest!
It was given to me!
Stand still! Hands up in the air!
No! Ah! Ah...
What... What's this, then?
There's nothing wrong with having that in my pocket! It's a Grammer buddy! We're friends!
Does it live under humane living conditions?
Yes, it lives in a nice little shoebox, it's really happy there!
So that's why you should not arrest me, Officer!
Okay, okay, I believe you.
Ah! Ah! Ah...
What's this?!
Wait... It's an Otomo! Why do you have an Otomo?!
No reason! They...
Are they friends?
They're friends! He was on a playdate, obviously! He came to visit the shoebox, so that's why!
Am I free to go, Officer? Am I free...
I'm starting to think that maybe... maybe it's okay. Let me... let me see one more time.
Ah! Ah! Ah...
What's this?!
Nothing... It's nothing.
Oh... Oh...
Can't a girl have some BL in her pocket?
Kimi ni Dunk...
I mean, can't a girl have some hobbies?
Okay, I see.
Can't I read? Am I not allowed to read all th--
Ah! Ah! Ah!
Stop making those noises!
What's this?!
Another one?!
This one is a catboy, and then the other...
Have you heard of that really, really awesome manga where whenever they...
Okay, okay...
On the floor! On the floor! On the floor! Get it off the floor!
Ah... Ah...
What... Ah...
Stop making those noises!
What's this?!
What's this one, then?
So this is a one-shot... I really, really like this one.
So you see these two men right here? One of them is Omega, another one is an Alpha.
It's called the Omegaverse. And then, they don't actually turn into wolves here, it's just...
It's called pack dynamics, and one of them is really, really dominant...
...and the other one is really submissive, and then one of them can get pregnant!
Do you like... Hello? Are you listening?
Officer? Officer? One of them gets pregnant, it's really, really...
The next training is Apprehension Training.
This is a critical close-quarters task in the field,
requiring officers to approach and subdue a target swiftly.
However, unexpected behavior on site can sometimes shake one's judgment.
Can Justice successfully and reliably subdue the target?
Gigi and Raora's Apprehension Training!
You have three minutes. Begin!
Yeah! You're going down, criminal scum!
Oh, no! Ah! No, please!
Put your arms behind your back! Put your arms behind your back!
Why would you do that?
Put your arms behind your back!
I mean...
Get her! Get her!
You're a criminal!
Look at my tail. Look at my tail. Don't you like my tail? Don't you like my tail?
Don't fall for it!
I'm unsure who's winning.
Don't tempt me!
Hey, Gigi! Don't fall for that!
You know, you cannot hurt me.
You are Justice!
You don't really want to hurt me.
Show me your back!
Kill her!
That's how we do it.
Oh, now you have the right to remain silent.
Oh, no, no, no. You don't want to hurt me, do you?
You're a criminal, so I'm gonna have to touch you.
She's going to enjoy that.
I'm gonna have to put you in jail.
Oh, that's evil. Why would you put me in jail, Gigi?
Stop... Stop...
Ask for handcuffs!
Oh! No!
Help! Help! She's killing me! Kill her! Kill her!
Gigi! Stop! Stop! Gigi!
Oh, Gigi, why would you... Why do you want to touch my tail? Hey! That's my tail!
Show me your tail!
Ah! Stop!
Stop! You're a criminal! You're a criminal! You're a criminal! You're a criminal!
Down, Raora!
Don't look... Don't look.
Ah! Ah! Ah...
Get back down! Get back down!
Down! Where are you going?
You would never touch me, right?
No, I would touch you. I will touch you.
I will touch you. I will hurt you.
Lie- Lie down. Lie down, you're a criminal!
You're a criminal, so you have to lie down!
You have to do what I say, 'cause I'm the police!
I'm a loser. Wait, I have something here. Hold on.
Oh, my clothes, my...
Hit him! Hit him!
I'm trying! I'm trying!
Get back on the ground!
Oh, you wanna be here next to me?
Why are you on top of me?! Get off!
Both of them are terrible at this.
You get off me!
Kiss me! Kiss me! Kiss me!
Kiss me!
I win! Guys, I win!
Okay, okay, okay. I think that's enough.
That's enough!
That was... that was apprehension.
Did I win?
Who do you think won, Liz?
Wow.
And the winner is...
Wait, this is about apprehension training. There's no winner.
Did you do a good job apprehending her?
I am still free!
In the end, you apprehended her.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I got her in a leg lock and everything.
I think she's correct. You're definitely interlocked.
Hey! Hey, hey, hey! Kill her!
You know, I disqualify. Gigi's the winner.
Yay!
Well done, Gigi, well done. You apprehended the...
No, no, I think you won.
Yeah, Gigi, that was really good. I think you won too.
Hey! Hey! Not without my consent!
Okay, okay.
Elizabeth and Cecilia, apprehension training!
You have three minutes! Are you ready?
Well, one- one second, here we go.
Flame on! Flame on!
I'm ready.
Flame on!
Flame off!
Are you guys ready now?
We're ready. - Yes.
Okay. Three, two, one, start!
Suspect! Suspect, stop right there!
I am Evil Elizabeth, and I have put chewing gum in everyone's hair!
How evil am I?!
Hands up in the air!
Hands up? Oh, yeah, yeah!
Oh no! Oh no! Oh no! Oh!
Help! Help!
Oh my god Liz, you should kill her.
She's so strong.
Liz! Liz, I've fallen!
Oh, look, come on. Up, up, up. Come on, up again.
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay, you did great. You want another go?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh! Oh no, I've fallen!
I'm doing it!
Okay, okay. All right.
Did I win, Liz? Did I win?
Are you willingly going to come with me to the police station?
Oh no, cuz I'm evil! I'm going to go burn a village.
Wait, stop!
Look at this!
Oh my goodness! I am evil, and she is evil! She's evil! She's the most evil!
Oh my goodness, is that a signed picture of the evil, evil, evil Nerissa Ravencroft?!
Give it! I need it!
If you come with me, I'll give this to you.
Yes! I will, yes! Yes!
Okay, hands behind your back, hands behind your back.
I get the picture though, right?
Yes, of course. Yes, of course. Here you go.
Yes, yes, yes!
You were playing dirty! You just humiliated Liz!
No, I am a smart, smart cop!
And instead of using violence, I used my brain!
Justice loses!
Now we can never get... we can never get justice!
Uh, I don't know what you're on about, and yeah, yeah, you did really well! I think you did great.
You, uh, you know, used a weapon against, uh, the suspect to, uh...
...appre- apple- appletention... apprehen-
Apprehend them.
And, uh, yeah! So I think you did great.
Um, yeah. Great job, Cecilia. I think Cecilia has done the best out of everyone here personally.
You can't film this! - Yeah, film this.
You see, Justice's greatest weakness...
No! No! You weren't supposed to win! Justice is cooked!
We're never going to catch criminals like this!
The second training is Interrogation.
It's a crucial investigative tool...
...process, where even the slightest inconsistencies in a statement must be detected to get closer to the truth.
Can Justice remain unaffected by the situation...
...and accurately draw out the information?
Yeah. I'm the best, actually.
I have a gun, and I know how to use it, so...
Easy. Don't worry about it, I have my ways. I've been here for so long.
It's going to be the easiest case of my life.
No, I don't think so.
Because my heart is too pure, and my ass is too fat.
And I'm not a gaslighter like Cecilia Immergreen.
I'm I'm not very confident, but I'll do my best.
Well, well, well, likely criminal!
We are about to begin your interrogation!
Wait a minute, I'm not a criminal. Why me? I haven't done anything.
What exactly have I been accused of?
Th-that would be the s-s-suspected identity fraud...
...a-and the unlawful acquisition of personal...
Come on, Gigi!
...of Nerissa Ravencroft!
I don't know anything about that. I'm innocent. Who is Nerissa Ravencroft?
Have you ever seen Nerissa Ravencroft?
You know who Nerissa Ravencroft is!
Come on!
No, I've never seen her in my life.
Blue, black long hair, red eyes?
Tell her that we saw her!
If I ever saw such a maiden, I would call her witchery.
She sounds like one.
Well...
We have evidence! We have evidence!
Does the name 99_x3_xd ring a bell to you?
Oh, yes, because "99_x3_xd" is me.
Huh! Ooh!
I knew it! You are the prime suspect in the stalking incident...
...of Nerissa Ravencroft!
Go, Gigi, go! Attack!
We have it on paper right here, and we have all the chat logs...
...that you put in Nerissa Ravencroft's channel right here!
I don't know. I watch I watch a variety of virtual entertainers.
"Nerissa Ravencroft, I'm outside of your house right now."
Tell her!
"Nerissa Ravencroft, I see you from the window."
"Nerissa Ravencroft, take off your shirt."
Whoa, now.
That was you, wasn't it?!
I don't know about that.
We also have pictures on the phone!
I don't know about that. I think you're mistaken. I would never speak that way to a princess.
Tell her that we're we're never going to give her donuts ever again!
Pinch her!
And you will never have donuts ever again!
And I will have never Do- Donuts? How did you know I liked donuts?
No more donuts! No more donuts!
But But if you if you if you just confess...
...we have an in with Nerissa Ravencroft...
Yeah, offer a good deal. Pretend!
...and we can give you what you want!
A date with Nerissa Ravencroft!
Okay, now you guys switch roles. Gigi is the bad one.
Look, I admit it. I know who...
Answer us right now!
Hey. Go crazy, go crazy on her!
Aaaah! Aaaah!
I'm scared.
Hey, yo!
Whoa.
Excuse us.
A third woman. It is my lucky day.
Chief Raora!
Oh, Chief Raora!
What do you guys think you're doing, huh?
I was doing what you were saying.
You're useless! You don't do anything in this place!
That's not true.
Why did they hire you, huh?
Because we have a lot of passion.
You're so useless!
This person... We have all the evidence! And you still didn't manage to make her tell the truth!
Chief, we're trying our best, okay? We aren't even paid! Overworked!
You're embarrassing us in front of the criminal!
Well, maybe you should do better than this!
You're not even listening to me, are you?
You never fix our coffee machine! And we never get daytime off, Raora! Chief Raora, I mean!
If you work more, maybe you will deserve your coffee machine.
Okay, okay.
Do you like coffee?
No.
Well, what do you want from me?!
I want info...!
Silence!
You know, one of my favorite virtual entertainers, Cecilia Immergreen, she does not like coffee.
Do you remember what did you do in ERBO?
Um, I I mean I I make up my own stories in my head.
Well, your own story with Nerissa Raven... was many times!
Yeah, get her, Boss! You're the boss.
Whoa.
You're the boss.
I think I think you will all witness at this.
I'll leave it up to you guys.
Yeah, I think you're doing great.
Thank you.
So you do know Nerissa Ravencroft!
I know that her name spelled backwards is Assiren.
How do you know that?! How do you know that?!
I know many Nerissas, because I'm very popular with the ladies.
Oh, what did you say?!
Ask her about the photo collection she has in her room.
We have some things that I want to show you, okay? This paper right here...
Can you loosen my shackles, please?
No.
These are all the photos that we found in your room that you have taken of Nerissa Ravencroft!
Do you recognize these?!
...these photos?
Do you recognize these photos of Nerissa Ravencroft? Well...
You took them! We found them on your camera!
I think my mother, where we like similar with Nerissa Ravencroft...
I think my mother, where we look similar with Nerissa Ravencroft...
That was not your mother!
Oh, there's a selfie right here!
Oh. That's you right there!
What do you think? It's you, it's you!
So, what do you have to say?
Is that you or is that not you?
I think there's an imposter here.
Tell her about the evidence that we have the bra with the wrong size,
so it's not hers, it's from Nerissa Ravencroft, because it's also signed by her!
We found a bra in your room.
And it's the wrong size.
I checked your breast size when you came in.
I would. And it's not this size.
It is Nerissa Ravencroft's!
Tell her that it's blue! She never wears blue!
And we know you don't wear blue bras.
'Cause I checked.
I think you guys should be arrested.
Stop it, criminal! I mean...
We can give you more than a bra from Nerissa Ravencroft.
We can give you way more than a bra from Nerissa...
It's Gigi's fault. Gigi's fault.
It's me!
That's her.
What are you doing to her?! What did you offer just now?
I was doing...
You hurt me! It was all her!
I was doing what you were telling me to do!
Time to get away.
She was talking about the bra!
You're trying to forget! That is really weird.
We are not trying to find a new victim!
You told me to do it!
What are you doing?! Why am I even paying you right now?!
Q. How was the interrogation?
All they do is just yell at me...
It was my first day on the force, and I just really wanted to be a good cop.
And 99X3XD is just too good! Even if we had all the evidence and all, she managed to steal...
Q. How was the interrogation?
I've never seen such a thing.
99X3XD was just so cunning, and...
it was kind of attractive, actually.
Those long hairs, and...
those curves. Actually, I should go find her.
Q. How was the interrogation?
Oh, they are totally useless. They can't do anything.
I need to find new people for this job.
They don't have the guts for this. Yeah.
But 99X3XD...
She said that she likes ladies and stuff. Maybe she would like me. Maybe she could work with me. Who knows?
Hm. What is she anyway?
Q. How was the interrogation?
Heh, they didn't see it coming.
They didn't know I was, well, they didn't know I was 99X3XD.
But they didn't crack me one bit.
For I am too good, I am too cunning, I am too powerful, as they say.
Can I get out of this?
The next training is Firearms Training!
What's required is precision and split-second judgment.
A moment's hesitation can greatly impact the outcome.
Can Justice remain unfazed by the situation and deliver highly accurate shots?
Firearms Training, let's go!
Let's go!
First, let's go over the rules!
A variety of targets will appear one after another.
Your job is to quickly decide whether to shoot or hold your fire!
If it's a valid target, take it out with your revolver.
But be careful: not every target is meant to be shot!
Out of the 10 targets, three are no-shoot targets!
So don't let your guard down!
Okay. Okay, okay. We got it.
What do you mean?
I wasn't listening. I wasn't paying attention.
All right, so Cecilia... So we shoot everything.
No! Shoot everyone!
Most importantly, shoot your friends.
Huh, what the freak?!
Aye-aye, sir! All right, Cecilia, you're up first!
Justice! Just like that!
Justice! Shoot that!
Cecilia, are you feeling confident?
Really good. Look at my trigger... Oh it's not... Oh yeah, I'm really good.
I'm gonna shoot everything, look. And I'm gonna win!
Ready, set...
Go! Whoa! No, no, no!
You saw? Oh, there it is.
Whoa, good job!
Yeah! I got it, I got it!
She's crazy!
Oh! Oh my god, is that a gnome?
With magic mushrooms? Wait, no, it's dead!
You killed him! Yay!
Fairy mushrooms? Magic fairy gnome.
Is that a pizza? Pizza!
Shoot the pizza! Pizza!
Pizza is a good thing, though?
Wait, why are we supposed to shoot pizza?
Uh-oh, oh no, no, no! Don't shoot!
Nooo!
No, she was just a little girl! Why? No!
She was just a little girl!
Oh, that's a royal guard!
NO! CECILIA!
Hey! Ah, she's a killer!
Oh! He's texting whilst driving!
Dead! That's good, we got rid of a criminal.
Yeah, that's the criminal right there. Hey, that's my pension!
Oh yeah, shoot that! Shoot her pension!
Yeah! Woo!
Hello, tiny jetpack. That's very tiny.
Yeah! Yay! That's a good shot!
Cucumber? Look at that dancing cucumber!
Go, little cucumber, go! Cucumber!
NO! CECILIIIA!
Wait... Yeah, we...
He's stealing the cookies!
Why is he stealing?!
I did it! You shot everything!
Yeah! Woohoo!
Cecilia's final score is... brrrrr... SEVEN POINTS!
Seven? Yeah, seven! Seven!
Hey, why is it...? Eight, nine... Aw...
Well, even if I... honestly?
I think the cucumber was a minus, and I thought it was a plus,
because we want to kill the cucumber so she doesn't have to eat it.
I don't like cucumbers, right!
And I think even if I shot the ones that weren't meant to shoot, sometimes...
in a crisis situation, you just have to make a decision, even if it's the wrong one!
I'm not sure about that. Deep, that's deep, boss.
All right, let's go! Flame on! Flame! Ahahaha!
All right.
Three, two, one, go!
Go! Yeah!
Okay, shoot it! Shoot it! Shoot it!
She's a true leader.
Shoot it! Shoot yourself!
That was me with a mustache!
How could you shoot yourself? Obviously not that.
No, no, that's the bird.
Yeah, that's the bird up there. Yeah, that's nice bird.
Oh, yeah, haha. Oh, it's you again!
Headshot! That was me with a mustache.
Okay. Ah, look...
Look at that bird's back over there! Wow! Haha.
Oh, is that a penny on the ground?
Why is she shooting that? I don't know. What sort of training is this?
My pension! We need that! Shoot it, shoot it!
We need that! We need that for Justice!
Oh, my pasta! Pasta?! My pizza! I'm hungry.
No, pizza!
Yeah! Pizza on the go! Tasty!
Okay, keep going.
Money, money, money! Shoot that, we need that! We need that!
Money! We need money! Money!
Why?! What?! We need money!
What? Oh, no, Liz.
Oh, look at that... Look at that gremlin! Kill it!
Kill it! Kill it! Kill it! Kill it!
That's so funny though!
Shoot me! Shoot it, shoot it!
Ta-da! Good job, boss! Yeah!
So good! Okay, you are done!
Oh yes! Okay, now what is my score?
Your points... Ah, drumroll! Brrrrr... NINE!
Nine! Nine points!
No points? No, nine!
NINE POINTS! Yeah! Nice point! Wow, okay.
Flame on! Flame on! Wow...
Yosh! Nyaah! Ah! Whoa!
All right! Nyaah! Ah! Whoa!
Okay, I got it. Your aim is so bad!
I just fell down. Don't, Liz. Haha.
Hey, how are you feeling, Gigi? Are you confident? I'm confident!
I'm confident! I'm confident! Okay, go on! Get them!
Three! Two! One! Go!
Oh! Ah, look!
That was so resonant!
How could you? That gun's not real! The gun's not real!
Money, money, money! That's money. That was good.
Get the money! That's not real! Yay, money! Yay, money!
Okay, keep shooting. Oh, money! Money, money, money, money, money!
Money, money, money!
Perfect! We need money. Ah! I had to kill it!
Gigi, why?! YES! YES!
That was just a baby! Kill the baby. A jetpack.
Go get it, go get it! Shoot that, shoot that tiny...
Kill it! This damn tiny jetpack! Why is it so tiny?
Yaaay! Yay!
Error processing subtitles for this segment.
Aahh! Loser!
And the loser, loser, loser...
Oh yeah, that's right! She's the loser!
It's okay, Liz. You're definitely the loser.
I just wanted to make you win because I'm the strongest with my god eyes, so...
Look, Cece doesn't look good.
What do you have behind your back?
What's that behind your back?
What do I have behind my back?
What's that behind your back?!
Get through this! Get through that!
She's mad!
Cece! Cece!
Take her down! Take her down!
The next training is Traffic Enforcement Training.
This duty requires accurately assessing the violation and processing it correctly.
However, in the field, unexpected behavior can sometimes shake an officer's judgment.
Can Justice stay unfazed in any situation and carry out the appropriate response?
Woohoo! We did it, Boss!
Good job, my goon!
Oh, no!
My goon, goon, do the voice! Do the voice!
Buonasera.
Good evening.
Good afternoon! What's all this, then?
Do you know why I pulled you over?
That was really cool!
Oh my god, here they are again. Silenzio!
Oh my god, here they are again. Silence!
Don't act like you don't know anything!
You blew right through the stop sign!
Oh, we are just really in an early hurry right now!
Oh, we are just really in a hurry right now!
We're on a ride! My husband, he's pregnant!
Hang on. Can I see your driver's license, please?
Um, yes, yes.
Do you have your driver's license?
We don't have time! He's really pregnant!
And his water just broke!
And we have to go to the hospital...
...right now, please!
You're a liar!
We're not... We're not lying!
He's like, really pregnant. Look how big he is!
I think he's not pregnant at all.
Excuse me, my husband is really pregnant. He's really big right now.
I am. Let him feel! Please.
Let me feel the baby.
It's kicking!
My son! I feel you!
Silenzio!
Silence!
Please!
Don't you think those two are acting a little bit suspicious?
I don't know, Boss. Mamma mia.
Are you all right? Do you think... Could it be?
Yes! See? This is exactly what I was thinking.
Yeah.
My son! No, no, no!
Yes! You just ate him! It was the baby!
There was a horse in there!
No, it was my baby! It was our baby!
Recently...
...I heard the sound coming from the trunk.
Hey! You can't say that about my baby!
Mind if we take a look at the trunk?
Wait, wait, wait, wait! You can't!
Don't do it! Don't do it!
We're just going to take a look at that trunk.
You are definitely guilty!
No, you can't! You can't!
Freeze yourselves! Stop in the name of the police!
You startled me! Is that...
A horse?! It's a horse!
It's not a horse! It's my son! It's our son!
Gigi Murin! Cecilia Immergreen! You're under arrest!
No, wait! Take me! Take me!
I can't be under arrest! I have too much to lose!
Yeah, you're under arrest! Give me your hand!
You are arrested, officially!
Wait, Boss! Boss! You can't leave me! Boss!
I'm already arrested! See you later, losers!
Boss! Cece! Boss!
We're going to get him! Go, go, go!
Let's get her! I can't drive!
It's just you and me, baby.
National Museum
All right, the place is empty.
Got about ten minutes before the guard's next patrol.
So this is the YAGOO trophy...
The Giga-Mega National Treasure.
I'm going to make a fortune on this.
This is Justice.
Is this an emergency?
Help! Help, please! Can you please help us?!
Please help somebody right now!
I don't know what to do!
Calm down and take a deep breath.
Can you tell me exactly what happened?
Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame
Uh, calm down...
Calm... down...
Ow, my ears...
Leave it to us.
Justice is on the way right now.
Everyone, we have a case.
The Ultimate National Treasure has been stolen!
Head to the scene immediately!
The Ultimate National Treasure?
You mean the YAGOO statue?
Who'd even want that?
Just let him keep it.
Gigi Murin
Gigi, that is disrespectful!
It is still the Ultimate National Treasure!
We're counting on you.
Fine, I'm on it.
Ah! Wait, Liz!
The super limited edition satani plushie drops in just three minutes!
It's limited quantity, okay?!
That means I absolutely have to buy it!
Okay, so only two minutes left now...
Just go already!
No! Oh, mio Dio!
No! Oh, my God!
Aspetta un attimo!
Wait a second!
Just...
Raora Panthera
Cecilia, did you get any information?
Cecilia!
Hold on!
Who the hell changed my keyboard to American?!
Cecilia Immergreen
Glad you loved my present, Cece!
This was you?!
You little piece of sh—
You absolute garbage can!
When I get you, I'm going to f—
Cecilia, every second counts here.
I know, I know!
All right, found a backdoor on the palace server.
Cracking the encrypted protocol via brute force,
and forcing the security patch overdrive on the mainframe system security data...
English, please!
Fine. I'm in!
The suspect is a woman dressed entirely in black.
Height looks around 168 centimeters.
She really likes people wearing helmets.
Oh! She's fleeing north!
If you move now, you can still catch her!
You all heard her!
Let's move out and apprehend the suspect!
For Justice!
Raora, what are you doing? You're not even driving!
You don't know how to drive a car?!
What? Put your foot on... on the gas pedal! - What?!
Wait! Stop! - Why did you wait?! - Look!
There is a horse in front of us! - There's a freaking horse in front of the car!
Oh my god, there's a freaking horse! - Oh, big horse right there, oh my...
It's wearing a mask!
Look at the mask! Seriously?!
No way, that's a real horse!
How am I supposed to get out of here now?!
Oh, you... How are we gonna get home?
I might not be able to get my limited edition spiedini for Halloween this time!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait! Horses like vegetables, right?
I think there's a cucumber in the trunk!
A what?! - A cucumber! In the trunk!
For the horse! For the horse!
Hold on, Gigi Murin. Why do you have a cucumber in your pocket right now?
Gigi Murin... You know why.
You know why! - What?
Gigi Murin, you know I hate cucumbers.
Why do you have cucumbers right now?! - Just hold on...
Ew! Get out of here!
You know where I'm going to put that cucumber? - Where?!
Get out of here right now!
I don't want to see that cucumber! Ew!
What about the horse? What about for the horse?
No! - What about for the horse? Oh, so you hate me!
Now you freaking hate me! You hate me! So you hate me!
So you hate me! Just say it! Tell me!
You freaking hate me! You hate me! - You know I hate you when you tell me that you've got cucumbers...
...and I hate cucumbers, and I know that I hate... and I hate that cucumbers that they're inside...
...and they will put that cucumber... we talked about that many times, and now...
Haah... Those two are away with the fairies!
Cecilia! Do you have any updates on the suspects' location?
Mmh, you're so close! Haha!
Cecilia?
Wait... Wipe...
Cecilia Immergreen!
No! I missed!
Look what you did, Liz! You ruined my perfect score!
I was so close!
Aaaah! Not you, too!
Haah... Ah... Did I fail them as a mother?
My heart breaks as their big sister.
I've done everything in my power to look after those three!
Those three wild, eccentric little sisters...
...and guide them to this very day.
I gave them my all!
Oh... What did I do to deserve such cruelty?
Where did I go wrong?
Where did my guidance stray away from the path?
Oh...
You three were still... still there, huh?
We're sorry... - Mommy...
I promise I will be a good girl!
Mommy... - Big sister! - Big sister! Big sister! Big sister!
It's just allergies! I'm not crying, you're crying!
Thank you, big sister! We love you so much!
Happy ever after! - Yay!
Justice is just like that.
Justice didn't get that...
Guys! Everyone!
It's the thief who stole the ultimate YAGOO statue!
Ohh! We're gonna kill them! - What the freaking...
Kill them! Kill them!
Hey, you! Hold it right there!
Because of you, I missed out on a limited edition spiedini and I didn't even get to eat my delicious pizza!
Haaaah... How are you going to take responsibility for this?!
That sounds like a you problem. Go eat your pizza now.
Oh, by the way, there's a shop nearby famous for its cucumber pizza.
It's to die for.
Eh?! Cucumber pizza?!
Yeah. - Eww...
Even I've had it before. Absolutely exquisite.
This is... Haah... This is such an insult!
Impossible!
It's okay, it's okay, don't worry, relax, relax, relax!
Doom!
Doom?
Justice Shopping!
Whoa!
And now, it's time to introduce Justice's 2nd Anniversary Merch!
Yay!
First, take a look at this!
The Premium Acrylic Message Board!
Whoa!
We spoke with someone who actually used it.
Oh? You want to meet...
...to talk about the Premium Acrylic Message Board?
Ah, yeah! Yeah, sure. Um, oui, oui.
Uh, this artwork is so cool! I love it so much.
Uh, using acrylic instead of papier was such a good choix!
And it makes it feel really special.
And the foil-stamped replicated messages,
that's honestly the best part!
I can't stop looking at it.
It just looks that much good, you know? Oui, oui.
Uh please, support Justice and buy their merch!
Oui, thank you. Merci.
Wow! That's some pretty high praise!
We've still got lots more merch to introduce,
so let's move on to the next item! Here it is:
Embroidered Patch Keychain!
So cute!
The illustrator behind this artwork is none other than Raora Panthera!
And guess what? We've received a special message directly from her!
Ciao! This is Raora Panthera, the artist behind the Embroidered Patch Keychains! Rawr!
You know, I'm I'm so happy I got the chance to draw for my Justice girls!
Creating something for my friends always feels really special,
and and I hope I I hope you're gonna love them as much as I do!
Sì, sì, sì!
And you know, they took all my adorable illustrations and turned them into those cute embroidered keychains!
And you know, since they're since they're keychains, you can attach them to your bag and take them with you wherever you go!
Yeah, a little bit extra cuteness for your everyday life!
So make sure to pick one up, and trust me, the cuteness is guaranteed!
Yes! Look at that, they are so cute! Adorable!
What a wonderful piece of merch!
Anyone would love to have that one in their home, including me!
All right, let's move on to the next piece of merch. Take a look at this:
The Medal-Style Badge!
Cool!
We caught up with Justice's leader, Elizabeth, to get her thoughts.
Hm? You want to hear about the badge? Of course!
My sweethearts, my Justichads...
This badge was designed with the image of law enforcement and authority in mind.
The weighty, prestigious look fits Justice perfectly, don't you think?
I think it looks absolutely fantabulous! It looks fantastic. Very cool.
Anyone who strives for justice should definitely get their hands on one.
Oh, and it also comes in a beautiful display box, so it's perfect for displaying and admiring as well.
I hope when you guys look at your your medal, or wear it,
that you will remember how us, Justice, are
so proud of you all, and we all really appreciate you so, so, so much.
So I really hope that comes to mind every time you wear or look at this medal.
Yay!
And that was a message from Elizabeth!
And now, for the final item we're introducing today... Here it is:
The Double-Zip Patch Hoodie!
Whoa!
We spoke with a fan who actually got their hands on the merch.
Wait, a Justice show?! Oh, oh my god! Oh my god, I'm so excited!
You want to hear my thoughts on this merch, as the biggest Justice fan in the world,
that has nothing to do with Justice, I'm just a random fan passing by?
Of course! Ask me anything!
Oh, I absolutely love the design!
The patches inspired by all four members of Justice, they're so cute and stylish!
And I love how each one of them reflects their personality.
And and the logo and the text on the back gives it such a cool, premium look.
It's the kind of hoodie that instantly makes you think,
"Mmm, yes, this is Justice!"
Oh, it's amazing!
The brushed fleece lining makes it super warm and comfortable.
Not only does it look great, but it's also really practical!
And the fact that it comes in both L and LL sizes is fantastic!
I think a lot of fans will appreciate having different size options.
So make sure to buy the Justice merch, okay?!
Wow, jolly good!
Now that's a passionate fan!
And that's it for Justice Shopping!
So, how was it?
It was awesome!
And what did you like the most?
The horse!
Ah, the horse... of course.
And this Justice news flash!
We interrupt your regularly scheduled programming
to bring you this breaking news.
We have just received an exclusive update from Justice, the global guardians of peace.
Rumor has it a brand new track from the iconic four-piece is about to drop at any second.
I repeat: new music from Justice is imminent.
Do not touch that dial.
We will be right back with the world premiere.
This is Ouro Kronii signing out.
Yeah
Are you there?
You're a SUPER GIRL
(JUSTICE JUST LIKE THAT,)
(JUSTICE GET GET THAT!)
If you're feeling trapped, send out a signal right above! (Gesundheit!)
We'll find you, set you free, then you can sign up for the club! (Innit!)
Danger, fun fun fun, soul shine like the sun
(MINNA HAPPINESS, MINNA HAPPINESS) Soul shine like the sun
(Everyone's happiness, everyone's happiness) Soul shine like the sun
The frig? I'm big! My strong strong muscle
They see me run, it's no miracle
You are shining SO BRIGHT!
Do your dancing LET'S FIGHT!
You can be a SUPER SUPER GIRL
I'm the SUPER-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA (Hey!)
DUPER-PA-PA-PA-PA (SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL)
SUPER-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA (Hey!)
Come sing with us, beating villains for fun <3 it (I'M SUPER GIRL)
Put on your antennas, get your super girl fit (YOU'RE SUPER GIRL)
I'm the SUPER-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA (Hey!)
DUPER-PA-PA-PA-PA (SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL)
I always want a pizza, stack those fries up to the sky (Ciao Ciao)
You lot say whatcha think about us hittin' town tonight? (Justice!)
Feeling happy time, no sad, say bye bye
(MOTTO MANIAC, JUSTICE JUST LIKE THAT!) No sad, say bye bye
(Even more maniac, Justice just like that!) No sad, say bye bye
So stomp, stomp, stomp your feet to this beat
’Cuz we are space, no, no gravity!
You are shining SO BRIGHT!
Do your dancing LET'S FIGHT!
You can be a SUPER SUPER GIRL
I'm the SUPER-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA (Hey!)
DUPER-PA-PA-PA-PA (SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL)
SUPER-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA (Hey!)
I know you're feeling so super bad
You don't have depression, you're just super sad
We are change the world, that's hope! If you doubt, hope you explode
Justice loud, Justice proud and we keep telling you!
We are SUPER-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA (Hey!)
DUPER-PA-PA-PA-PA (SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL)
SUPER-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA (Hey!)
Justice we are justice, make the baddies go boom! (I'M SUPER GIRL)
Come on, come on baby, rocket ship to the moon! (YOU'RE SUPER GIRL)
I'm the SUPER-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA-PA (Hey!)
DUPER-PA-PA-PA-PA (SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL)
SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL
And that was Supernova Super Girl, our brand new song!
Yay!
And just like that, our second anniversary stream is coming to an end.
So, what did you all think? We'll start with Raora this time.
Eh? Me?
Yeah, you first this time!
Ah, it was really fun, it was amazing! I can't believe it's been already two years, guys!
I know! Aah!
Thank you so much to you guys as well for being the best, the best companions ever, you know!
Yeah! Yay!
I'm so grateful to you guys. And thank you to JustChat for supporting us since two years now! It's insane, thank you so much!
Thank you, JustChat! Bye-bye!
Thank you very much, everyone, for being—
Oh, sorry! / Oh, sorry!
This is yellow and green!
Thank you very much for being here today, everyone!
Thank you for two years! Thank you, Justchas!
Yeah!
Please keep supporting us and listen to our song!
Yes! Stream "SUPERNOVA SUPERGIRL"! / Supergirl!
What do you think, ERB? / What I think?
What I think? I think the stage is very cool!
Look at the stage! Wow!
And look at this amazing team. I can't ask for better...
...girls! Girls, I love you all very much!
And Justchas, we love you all very much, too!
Thank you so much for supporting Justice!
Thank you so, so, so much!
We love you so much!
So many kisses! You guys are so spoiled!
Okay, Gigi!
Nom, nom, nom, nom...
Are you eating them? She's eating them! / Oh, my god!
Hey, Justchas! Thank you for supporting us for two years!
Two! We didn't even know we could—
I didn't even know Raora could count up to two!
Really, really? / Just kidding! But we made it to two years!
Thank you for supporting us! Please stream "SUPERNOVA SUPERGIRL"!
Learn the chants!
Learn the chants for every song!
For some reason... all our chants! For some reason, maybe you should learn the chants!
I wonder if there's lyrics somewhere for you to learn...
...when we go "Supernova Supergirl"!
Or "Minna happiness"!
Minna happiness! / Yeah!
We all feel like Supergirls because of you guys!
Thank you so much, Justchas!
And don't forget to grab the merch!
Yes! Purchase! Purchase our merch!
Yes, thank you, thank you, thank you!
Thank you all so much for celebrating with us today!
Please keep supporting Justice, please, going forward as well!
Now then, let's all say goodbye together with our own chant!
Yeah! / You ready? / I'm ready. / All right!
Jus-tice! Just like that!
Jus-tice! Get get down!
Yay!
Minna happiness!
Minna happiness! Bye-bye!
Stay tuned for the premier of Justice's new MV
"SUPERNOVA SUPER GIRL" right after this!
Stay tuned for the premiere of Justice's new MV